Okay, so welcome everybody. So we thought we'd do just a really general call
today because
we've had a few newbies and it's always good to get a bit of a refresher
anyways in it
and get some inspiration and tips from each other on the basics which is what
to say and
do on come. So yeah, we had a bit of feedback which was, you know, asking this
question
and a lot of girls ask it, you know, when they're first starting out. So we
thought
it'd be good to do a call on it, bit of a training call on it, get some ideas
together,
have a bit of a chat and at the end of it, or even throughout, if you've got a
question
that you want to ask or something you're not quite sure around, just either use
the gesture
to put your hand up or just ask us a question to speak up and ask us a question
. We'll be
more than happy to stop and answer your questions and we'll come to you at the
end if anybody
else has got any tips that they want to share or any questions they want to ask
and we'll
make sure it becomes that. At the end, so let's get into it. Okay, so before we
get into we're
going to give lots of sort of tips and advice on what to actually say or do on
come. But
I think it's great just to go over, you know, briefly how we get ready and how
we set the
scene for ourselves and when we're coming on can. What we say and what we do is
obviously
important, but how we get ready, how we get into the right mind, what our
environment looks
like, there's a few things that we would think about before we even approach
what we're going
to say or do. That we'll just briefly talk about those first. Lovely picture.
Barbie girl
there. So prepping your surroundings, so really important to prep your
surroundings before
you go on camp. So depending on what your sort of alter ego is like or how you
present
on camp is going to depend on how you set your environment up to go on camp. So
for me,
I have a few different areas that I like to come in my house depending on how I
'm feeling,
what type of you know role I'm going to play that day. So I might set it up in
my sofa
area, I might be in my little office here, I might be on my kitchen table or in
the bedroom.
I like to make sure that's what we always say, we like to make sure that like I
am here,
we're taking up a big portion of the screen. Usually if I was coming, I would
have like
my camera a little further down so you can see more of my body, so I'd be
slightly more
away from the screen. And I'd be using my keyboard if I'm typing so that my
keyboard
is here so you can see more of my body and more of me in the screen. That's how
I'd prep
my surroundings. We have advice on the website about lighting and things and
lighting is
really important. As you can see here I'm quite well-lit, that's because I've
got a ring
light just behind my laptop. So it's really important to make sure that your
clients are
going to be able to see you nice and clearly because that's something that they
're going
to care about and that's going to make them stay. Obviously you can have things
in your
environment that are going to draw the clients in a bit more. So you might like
to think
about if you're in bed, you know, just having some lovely bedding, maybe a
little bit of
a backlight. I know George and I have some nice backlights. I know you've got
some nice
pink ones, aren't you, Jay? They just make it look really nice and sort of sens
ual and
girly and just set this in a little bit more. You can have things in the
background. So
if you do use any toys or any equipment or in some lingerie, just having things
lying
around in the background for people to look at but not making it too busy that
it kind
of takes away from you. So prep your surroundings and making sure in that that
you're comfortable,
it's really important to be comfortable when you're on cam because you don't
want to be
in a position that's going to be really awkward or you're going to get stiff or
you're not
going to come across as natural and relaxed as they're thinking about you're in
comfort
as well. Prepping your energy. So on a lot of our calls we talk about this and
it can
be different for everyone but it's really good to think about how you prep your
energy
to go on cam. So when we're coming on, I personally want to be quite connected
to my body so I
might just shift, do some stretches and make sure that I'm nice and connected
to myself.
Any stresses I've had or anything that's happened in the day, I like to just
put some
music on while I'm putting my makeup on and getting ready for cam just to make
sure that
I'm nice and relaxed and I'm in a good frame of mind. Anything that can just
help you to
loosen up and feel good within yourself because the way you feel about yourself
is going to
come across to your clients and it's really important. Would you say anything
else on
that G about prepping your energy? Is there anything that you do for that? I
normally
just like to have a moment of just gratitude and sometimes I think I really
want to make
this amount and put pressure on what I want to make. Then I'm like no I shouldn
't think
that way I should just come to gratitude and whatever's meant for me will come
for me.
You know what I mean? Whatever I'm meant to do on cam that day will, that's how
it will
be. That's what I probably do. Yeah that's a good idea actually. Thinking about
the client
that you want to attract that day because on different days it's different isn
't it?
Because some days I might be feeling something, some days something else. So
yeah, probably
part of prepping your energy is just welcoming in and feeling gratitude for the
clients that
you're going to have and even changing your tagline to reflect the kind of
you want to have that day to make sure that you're doing things to welcome in
those clients.
What to wear? So what to wear is part of course getting ready for cam. Putting
a bit
of a face on so usually I will put maybe a bit more makeup than I usually wear
on cam
just because for me and my style I think it looks better. But you can wear
whatever you
feel comfortable in. Quite often in the daytime we'll go on cam in my gym
clothes. Obviously
they're quite small, quite sexy gym clothes but they're really comfortable and
I tend
to do really well on cam when I'm wearing that. You can wear a lot of pyjamas,
you can
wear some fetish wear, nice lingerie. It's nice to have a couple of like sexy
little
layers that you can take off. So yeah, thinking about what you wear is also
part of prepping
your energy as well isn't it? Because you kind of inhabit the role and get your
creative
juices flowing. And checking in with your boundaries. So like I said, each day
might
look different on cam. Some days you might come on and just feel really energ
ised and
really raring to go and want to connect with people and whatever. Other days
you might
be a bit tired and you might have different ideas about what you want to do.
Some days
I go on cam and I might feel a bit horny and I'm just really wanting to connect
and maybe
massage or just be a bit sensual. And then other days I just really want to put
a cup
of tea and a bit of a chit chat and that's okay as well. So checking in with
your boundaries
is a good thing to do to get yourself ready to cam. Okay, opening the
conversation. Do
you want to go through this one Jay? Yeah. Okay, so there's no need to over
think how
you'll open up a conversation with someone who comes into your chat. A simple
hello,
how are you with a smile is a good start. And yeah, I think that when people
start they
really overthink that first cam session and they put a lot of stress and worry
on it.
But just logging in and just yeah just smiling how are you is more than enough
and then the
conversation will flow from there. And for retaining clients it's good to
welcome them
back and let them know you're glad they're here. Bonus points if you can
remember anything
about your last chat and reference that. So on the website, I feel as though
obviously
you do make money with new clients but you will really make most of your money
with your
regular clients and they're the ones who are going to keep coming back the year
after year
after year and keeping you in this job basically. So it is definitely important
to make note
of your regular clients and as it says there try to remember little things
about them,
about the chat, about what they might have been up to in between the chat, they
might
have said you know they've got things on with work or they're going on holiday
or whatever
it is and you can ask them about that next time they return. And this just
makes them
feel like they're special and that you've remembered obviously about them. And
that's
why they're here at the end of the day like we say this a lot but it's so true.
The clients
they want a connection, that is the main reason they're here. So if you've made
them feel
like you've remembered them then it honestly does go the longest way. Sometimes
it might
just be you pretend to let you remember because there's so many that you speak
to. And I know
I've been there before with they've said oh you know last time was great blah
blah blah
and I'm like yeah it was so great and then just not know what they meant what
they were
talking about. But then I would just say something like what was it about the
last conversation
that really got you going or something like that you know I'll ask them
basically what
are we talking about actually asking that. And I'd actually once there was this
one client
that was like I feel like he was trying to catch me out like he knew that I
didn't know
that it's only happened once all the times I've asked this so I think it does
normally
where they normally just tell you and say oh it was when you told me to you
know do this
or when you've done that whatever. But this one he knew I feel because he was
like oh
you know it was that time it was the thing that you'd always do and he was
speaking in
code and I was like oh my god just tell me. So yeah try to remember them and if
not just
try to act like you do and then try and figure it out along the way. And also
it's normal
to find some clients enjoyable to chat to and others a bit more difficult to
engage with.
Yeah you could say that again not for sure. If it makes you feel a bit more
confident
and gets the chat flowing you could share something about your day, a flirty or
funny
story is great or ask them if they like what you're wearing. So yes some
clients it will
just be like you're speaking to a brick wall like they'll give you nothing back
. So you
know you've got to try and basically have a conversation with yourself. So as
it says
there if you've got a little funny flirty story to tell them at least it's
something
you know to keep the conversation going or that I know that's something that
held us
a lot. You always have a little story right that you can whip out at any time
you need.
I think it's good to just have it in like you know in the back of your mind
just to use
in any part of the conversation that way it goes a bit dry and also yeah ask
them what
you like what you're wearing. I do this a lot as well if the conversation is
also going
a bit dry because then it puts the focus on you know your body what you're
wearing and
maybe get them a bit excited and then it'll float from there maybe they'll say
oh can
you twirl or can you can I see you with less on or this or that and if they do
ask those
things you can then ask for a private chat and if you're already in group let's
say you
can then say take me to private chat and I'll show you what it looks like
underneath or
whatever so it's always an upsell opportunity. So yeah is there anything you
would say on
that matter Elle? Yeah I was just thinking that that could also be part of the
prepping
and then getting ready for camp what it is for me that I have I think of a
little story
or a little thing that I'm going to say for that day so like a lot of the time
my outfit
will tie in with the little story that I've got and so like I went on a date
with a girl
today and we bought this lingerie together so I thought I'd come and wear it
like do
you like it and I'll put something like something that alludes to that story in
my tagline
as well or a lot of the time I wear my gym kit so I'm like yeah I just don't
know I work
out in the gym and I'm just getting really horny looking at the the Lycra the
other people
in the yoga class and so I thought I'd come online or just a little thing like
that and
sometimes I use like I'll ask them what they do or if they tell me something
about themselves
sometimes they'll say what they need for work or it'll say in the use name that
they
like cars or something I'll just make up that I've got a fantasy about that one
thing so
if they tell me like that they work at a certain place I'll be like oh I've
always had a voice
had a like fantasy about like whatever it is like that sort of workman and like
you know
just I'll just make up something to do with just taking one little tidbit from
the name
or something they said or whatever and just turning into a bit of a story so
yeah stories
for me I just think that's just such a great way if you if you're prepared and
you've got
a few things and you can use the same ones over and over I find them just a
really great
way for guys to connect with you to get something a bit different to find you
like engaging and
flirty and to get good regulars because then they keep coming back to you and
on that as
well there's a there's a training call I did do you remember the name right now
what was
it something about fantasy is it feels nice to see right in script one yeah
there was a
fantasy one yeah so you can catch up on that in there in the members area and
that gives
loads of ideas about different little stories that you make up and fantasy with
them and
I think that's a great idea though what you said about picking up something
from their
username or maybe something like they've told you what they work as and then
you know
saying you have a fantasy around and that because that'll just make them
straight away
think oh wow like she's she's into into me or into you know what I mean because
I'm like
in this job or whatever so yeah I'm going to take that tip thanks I didn't ever
do that
one that's a good one yeah you don't even have to have a whole lot you can just
talk
with the first little bit and then hopefully they've got you know they've got
something
upstairs they'll they'll help you elaborate on the story so like oh what do you
think
would happen at or whatever you know and then they're really they get some of
what they
like in there so then you can gauge what they like so keeping the chat flowing
so it's probably
worth saying before this slide that you can't always keep the chat flowing you
could have
the best chat in the world you could be the sexiest person online and there'll
be guys
that you just can't keep the chat flowing with so don't pressure yourself to
keep the
chat flowing with every single person especially if you're just in a really
dead chat you know
and it's stopping you from engaging with someone else who might be wanting to
come with you
so yeah it's not always you know on you to keep dead chat going and there will
be people
that you know like we say peepers that just come in and come out and it's not
your fault
if you can't get them to stay and they just come in for a few seconds because
that happens
with everyone however you know there are lots of things that you can do and it
's really
good to sort of upskill and do these trainings and look back on the trainings
on the website
and stuff to find different ways to keep the chat flowing so we chat about some
of them
so they want to chat what next your most important tool is your ability to
listen and
to tune into what they want you might start off some chit chat by asking if
they're new
to AdultWork or what they like about it yeah so quite often I'll ask them they
've been
here before you know if they've if they've ever met anyone if I don't work do
it as they
normally chat to just being curious about what they're doing here and if they
come here
very often it's a bit cliché but you can get some people to open up telling
them why
you're here so telling them you're here to explore or experiment or depending
on what
type of person you're showing up as online will be you know how you fill in the
gaps in
that one but you can tell them that you're here to you know you could play a
bit of damsel
distress you're here to make some money and you really love chatting to people
and you're
here to because you've always wanted to look do this certain fantasy or it's so
many different
reasons so just telling them about why you're here and maybe why you were
inspired to come
online today like I said earlier I might say like I was in the gym and like
maybe feel
hot and bothered so I thought I'd jump online or I just I've been in meetings
you know I might
like have a nice shirt and have a nice shirt on and like work clothes and just
be like I've
been in meetings I'm just back from a corporate trip or something so it's
something a little
bit that brings a bit of personality to you or makes you a bit unique you can
tell them
why you're online and as I said before asking them about they use a name or
telling them
about yours and so I'm sure as we know there are a lot of shit usernames which
you can't
rate you can't really say much about but some of them some of them are good and
you can
you can just be curious about oh I mean you know what does that mean and they
can start
to open up and tell you a bit about themselves and asking if they've read your
profile and
if so what they liked about it and I suppose this works better sometimes rather
than others
I mean it's judging by the clients that you've got you're never going to ask
the same questions
to the same clients right so you're going to get you're going to gauge their
energy and
to kind of see what they're like before you go in with any direct questions and
for me
I have a lot of people that come to me that have read through my profile that
want a certain
thing that want to engage and want lots of conversation if you're you know if
your profile
isn't set up for that if it's like you know busty blonde and it's a Friday
night and that
you know you might not be asking the same question so asking questions in
accordance with
the type of clients that your profile is bringing in is really important and if
you're getting
clients that are not really aligned with you then it's a good idea to change
your profile
to try and get the clients that you want so yeah asking if they've read your
profile
or pointing to bits on your profile can be a good way to keep the chat flowing
and engaging
them in a chat about your life of course you know you don't want to be telling
them that
you just put a load of washing on or something you want it to be flirty and
engaging but
yeah I might talk about dates that have been on sometimes real sometimes made
up or yeah
lingerie that are for or parties I've been to just engaging them and you can
take inspiration
from like TV or whatever you know you can just think about a character that you
find
sexy or that you like on TV and what is it that they've done recently and you
can just
play up for that you know use inspiration you can draw their attention to your
outfit
your surroundings or your body and so of course yeah you can you're using your
whole
self it's not just what you're saying it's how how you're looking what you're
doing that's
engaging them as well and so using a body and remember to play into your campus
owner
listen out to any clues they're giving you about what turns them on or what
interests
you if you pick up any clues about them try to turn them into a question so
curiosity
that one word I think is like if I could give anyone advice about how you
engage people
on cam I would say stay curious don't think that you know already no two guys
are the
same you know there are trends about what what people want to chat to and what
turns
them on but everyone is different so staying curious about the person that you
're chatting
with and asking questions is is just such a good way to keep the chat flowing
and engage
them yeah I think I think how to pick up clues about what they like if you if
you if you
on cam you've got this idea in your head about what a cam girl is and what she
says
and how she acts then you can project and you're not fully actively listening
to what
they're saying but if you can just settle your energy a little bit and just
take the
pressure off yourself to be completely facilitating it and just remain curious
about what they're
saying the smallest of things that they say you can then reflect back to them
oh okay so
blah blah blah or what about this or oh what does that mean you know it's okay
also not
to know if they use a phrase or they're talking about something not only is
okay not
to know it's it's great not to know because most guys love educating you and
telling you
about something that they enjoy and so yeah just deeply being attentive and
listening and
asking questions. Okay so being seductive what it looks like definitely not
this so yeah
just wanted to say I would never come and come the way I look right now by the
way this
is just for training purposes only and am I still here by the way because all
your comments
for us I just want to make sure oh yeah I can still hear you yeah oh I think it
's she
isn't it I think it's her connection okay let me take over now then okay so let
's talk
about being seductive so what it looks like is body language and movement so
body language
so we've talked about taking up most of the screen like you might see here or
maybe having
the screen a bit further back so you can see more on my body when we're moving
we don't
want sort of big jerky movements or anything to look too harsh we want to be
slow and natural
and relaxed and we can use our body to be seductive and to tease so we can you
know
I might I might sometimes just turn a little bit this way or that I might laugh
or come
close to the camera in some instances and depending on what you're wearing you
can show
off what you're wearing as well so you might like to you know just just do a
little unveiling
or just some slow movements a hand across your body and there are lots of ways
that you can
use your body language and your movement to engage them so just remembering
that while
you're talking to them or while you're typing that they're looking at you they
're listening
to words but they're also looking at what you're doing so any small movements
are going
to help to engage them even more. Sorry Jay are you back? Sorry yeah it cut me
off them
then it kicked me off but I'm back now so yeah I can carry on if you like. Well
no worries.
Okay so teasing words and actions and so I suppose this would look different
for each
client and as some clients would like you to tease them by doing like motions
like this
if it's a someone who's into small penis humiliation whether someone who's not
into
that would have be like what the hell is she doing and so yeah it's always good
to find
out what your clients are into first and then you can know how to tease them
and you know
what to do with that and I think just like general tease and stuff that I
probably work
with most clients would probably be just you know putting like you're strapped
down or
something like that or just showing them your body or like you said I don't
know if you
just mentioned this now like you're breathing and stuff like that and as even
if you don't
like to have your mic on to talk it's good to put it on so they can hear your
voice and
I mean sorry hear your breath so hear you breathe in heavier after
conversations you
know going a bit more naughty or giggling after like funny stories or whatever
and stuff
like this is also part of seduction as well as it's like you know creating like
this fantasy
of like this yeah this like way that you're having with each other using sens
uality and
at your and your own pleasure so yeah a lot of our girls obviously like to
pleasure themselves
on cam so this is another way to be seductive on there with your clients and
it doesn't need
to be just pleasure in yourself and you know the obvious way it can be through
massage
or dance or just you know however you're feeling in that moment whatever's
going to bring you
pleasure and at the end of the day I feel as though the clients are there to
watch us
in pleasure whatever that is because a woman in living in a pleasure it's like
the most
beautiful thing so yeah I feel as though if you're just living in that state of
pleasure
your clients are gonna love it even on that one the other day like as an
example I realised
I had some like chocolate strawberries in the fridge and I was like oh I'm
gonna eat
them on cam that would be so good so I did I was just like slowly eating them
with like
the juice dripping down and it was so good I had loads of people in my group
chat and
just like I love that and you couldn't have your little snack while you were
eating you
know yeah yeah just just feeling pleasure yourself doesn't have to be like
sexual can
be like lots of different ways and it's enjoyable to watch isn't it yeah
exactly I'm always
eating on cam but it's normally like I'll show them a boob shot while I'm like
grabbing
someone to eat it like above the camp but that's a better way to do it it's
actually
eat something that looks quite sexy on cam I love that and patient and command
of the
room hmm what do you mean by this one L yeah so pacing is pacing to me is
really important
especially with certain clients so rather than I think that sometimes when
people are
a bit nervous they can go quite quick and like it would be like oh what do I
say next
what I say next actually it's okay to slow down because that gives you the
command of
the room sometimes so if you're slowing down say if I'm if I'm being quite dumb
on cam
then I would slow everything down and you know I'd be sort of checking in with
them
so how does that make you feel tell me tell me how it makes you feel you know
or so not
being too quick not having to rush I'll be too quick thinking about your pacing
because
it can be sexy to slow it down and it just shows that you've got control over
the room
you know or you slow down your like seductiveness and sort of build it up and
then get a bit
quicker and a bit faster if you're talking about certain fantasy you know sort
of getting
so pacing how slow or how fast you're chatting or moving can can be really good
you can
think it's something that you can play with to get clients to engage with you
more you
know and sort of bring your fantasies to life and your stories to life a bit
more
yeah perfect I love that and yeah okay and so power dynamics so this is like
like a lot
of clients will come into your room who are into like different power plays so
like the
sub and DOM power play and this could mean you're playing the DOM or the sub
depending
on what you're comfortable with and what you offer and what they want and so
yeah this
is very popular on cam to be honest it's basically my main way of coming is to
do I do domination
and that's a lot about the power dynamics and yeah it's so popular because I
feel as though
stuff like this especially the more extreme size of it a lot of the clients
they don't
want to do it in person with anyone so they come online to explore it with us
so if it
is something that you're into I want to learn like want to offer on cam it's
definitely
good to learn as much about this as possible as the more you know the more you
can offer
your clients and the longer the conversations will be and yet the more that you
know and
the subject the more safe the clients are going to feel in your care when you
're dominating
them and or even the opposite if you're and submit like being a sub submitting
to your
clients then it's good to know all about that because you don't want to go into
a feeling
as though and you have to do everything they say or whatever else it's good to
know like
you know your role in the sub DOM relationship as well and so yeah that's that
one okay and
slowly building up the tension so obviously on AdultWork we get paid by the
minute so
the slower that we are the better like the ends the main goal really is to keep
them in
your chat as long as possible and obviously you don't want to do it too slow to
the point
where they're like oh what is she doing is she ever going to just get to get to
it you
know what I mean but you'll gauge it with each client and you'll know your
intuition
will tell you like Elle said if you just let go of like the noise in your head
and just
take a moment come to your breath come to your body and just be in the moment
with the
clients be in that conversation try not to be anywhere else and just yes slowly
build
it up and use all of the things that we spoke about above your body language
your words
your actions your sensuality and yeah the I'm sure the clients will absolutely
love it
and yeah you can just build it up as much as you want and then bring it back
down again
and yeah as we said about the pacing just yeah use all of that stuff I won't
finally
using the sounds of your breath so I mentioned that a moment ago and the
clients do love this
a lot of the time and they might ask to hear you if you don't want to talk and
that's fine
and if they ask me to talk and I don't want to I'll just say I will take my mic
on and
I'll say a quick hello at some stage when you know somebody leaves the room up
I'll say
there's somebody around to that I'm not able to talk that's what I'll always
say if I don't
want to and but then I'll sit but then I'll say but I'll keep my mic on so you
can hear
and you know the sounds around me or whatever and they do genuinely love to
hear your breathing
and your laughing and you know whatever else just makes them feel a little bit
more connected
to you and also you can have music on as well and that can probably also add to
the feeling
of the conversation if you have a nice like sexy song on in the background it
obviously
will make you feel a little bit more in the moment and it might invite your
client to feel
that way as well and what are the benefits of being seductive so the client
feels safe
connected and enticed and it's also an invitation into a fantasy and this is
why the clients
are here as I just said a moment ago like they are here exploring these weird
and wonderful
fantasies that maybe it's the first time they've ever explored this with
anybody else and
yeah for a lot of them as well it's maybe fantasies that they've society has
put shame
on them to feel like you know to feel about like they feel shame about their
fantasy I
should say sorry due to society or due to whatever it is they feel shame about
it so
it's nice for us to allow our clients a safe space to explore this and yeah you
can got
your own pace and also yeah the sessions are longer which is exactly what we
want we want
nice long drawn out sessions and your sex appeal is centered which builds
confidence
so if you really just take your time with it and just tune into yourself and
just yeah
I think that is the most sexiest thing like someone who's just confident and
not trying
to rush your heavy phone just yeah and your clients will see that and your
clients will
keep coming back for more as we've said a lot of times it's the regular clients
that you want
and so yeah really just tuning into each client and what they want and just
giving them you know
a full experience with all the different senses you know not just what they can
see like you said
they can hear you and maybe you can have them like you know guide them through
touch on themselves
and and stuff like that I think it'll just yeah keep your kind of clients
coming back
yeah I like I like what you said about like I think it's good to keep in mind
that
but a lot of clients not all but for a lot of clients this is their only safe
space
like this is their only space where they can be completely themselves so just
asking them a
few questions and giving them a space where you're not going to judge them and
you seem
genuinely interested in them like that can be such a huge thing for somebody
who doesn't have that
in other areas of their life and I think that's something that we don't think
about enough you know
as CAM models is there yeah sometimes you're facilitating someone's like
authenticity someone's
confidence and it's a beautiful thing to be doing that for somebody isn't it
yeah definitely
so teasing and more so we talked a little bit about what to say but what to do
what can you
actually do um to tease on CAM so we've got a few ideas here so we can do
removal of layers
but like I said sometimes it's a good idea to just have a few little layers on
so that you can
remove them slowly one by one if that's something that you're comfortable to do
um games you can
even incorporate games into this so sometimes am I if I know Sophie talks about
this before and
I liked it in fact I think Sophie didn't you at one point Sophie had like a
spin wheel where you
could spin and it was like theirs or whatever which I really really like I love
that idea for like
being in group chat um but yeah different games you can make games with them um
you can I mean
anything you can think of that's fun and flirty and entertaining you can do you
know there are no
limits really um you can do massage or dancing massage is something that I've
done loads on CAM
if you have got the right lighting so maybe a bit dimmer a little bit dimmer
than my lighting here
um oil on your skin like looks so good like it just shines off your skin and it
looks so
sensual and nice and especially with certain materials and certain things that
you can wear
um you can even if you're into like if you if you want to get into it being
more dumb you can
use like latex or sometimes I like shine my latex on CAM some people absolutely
love that
um dancing obviously you can do strip teasers dances anything that you're in
the mood for
power play I know we've mentioned that a lot um so power play can be like you
know proper
doing a dumb session or being a subro session but it can also just be like you
know small little
role plays you know you can chat to someone and get to know them and as part of
that have just
little role plays where you'll be like pretending to be you know you might
pretend to be in an office
and they're the boss or you're the boss or you know just little power plays a
little role plays
where you're switching who's got the power um you can use toys or props there's
all yours so
depending on what you're doing you can use different things on yourself so even
if you don't want to
you know get properly naked or do playing or whatever you can use like um
things on your skin
so you can use like ice or you could use like feathers or anything that's going
to sort of
stimulate your skin um of course you can use sex toys and all of that kind of
stuff this is
kind of self-explanatory isn't it and there's the um what are they called the
ones that you
pull them to your cam what was it called? Love ants yeah so you can get um love
ants toys so the
clients can actually control your toy and they can tip you depending on um how
they control it
um so that's something that some girls have made really good money with or the
toys that they're
using so it doesn't have to be you using toys you can put their camera on and
you can be instructing
them about um you know whatever toys they're using um had someone the other day
this really lovely guy he's quite hot actually as well and he was just trying
on loads of underwear
for me and just like he had some toys there so I was asking him about what he
has there and what
he likes to do so I was getting him to show me what he likes to do and that was
a really long drawn
out session with a lovely person basically performing for me so if you can eat
you know if you fancy
getting into domination or you just want to play with it a bit that can be
great because it can
be the other person performing for you and you just facilitating that um and
roleplay yeah we've
talked about roleplay a little bit but roleplaken also involve what you're
wearing um and what we
haven't said on there is about uh fetishes as well so fetishes can be a big
part of teasing so
there are a lot of guys who have got fetishes so you might wear like different
socks or massage
your feet or different heels um so there are yeah there are a few fetishes um
so it's good to
ask people if they have any fetishes and be curious about what is they like
I think the best one was uh one of the girls and had that guy that used to like
her to put her
puffer jacket on so yeah I know I think he used to come back quite often and
she just put her puffer
jacket on for him speaking about the full fetish one I had a guy who had like a
sock fetish and
he bought me to wear as I say had I still have him but after all these years
his dog comes back
he wanted me to wear different colour and called socks so like a pink one and a
blue one say
michmash and then pretend to kick him in the balls so just stand back and just
kick the air
and just pretend like I'm kicking him in the balls and that's been going on for
years
like 10 years I'd say he's like literally since the stars of my webcam career
he's been
coming to me and asking me if you got any new socks any new uncle socks and
that's that that's
the fetish and he loves it I've got one that's been coming to me for years and
years and years
and he just likes me to put a bikini on and like flex all my muscles because it
's me behind the
behind the big profile of chicken we sit here and wrestle his wife but it's
been saying this
for like seven years and we have this little conversation about how I'm going
to wrestle his
wife and then I just show him that we're probably going to my fetish that I
loved like looking at
mostly bodies so yeah come understand why he's into that
so yeah our top tips um so I was thinking about what what my top tips would be
I think like I said
before I think the most important thing for me is curiosity like if you're
stuck if you're not
feeling that grey if you're like if you're just not sure then just to be
curious always the answer
just to be curious about the client because that's what they want they want
someone to be interested
in curious in them um I would say a million percent go and look at the courses
on the website because
every time if if I just am feeling a bit uninspired or whatever I just go on
there and just watch
one of them or a little bit of one while I'm getting ready and there's just
gonna be so many ideas
and tips and inspiration so definitely look at the training and courses
especially the dom
and the sub ones because it's really good ideas about what to say and do and
different games
you can play and and all the link go that you can learn um I think like
thinking about what makes
you unique is a really good idea because yeah if you if you can stand out from
other people that's
going to make you you know that's going to mean that they're going to hot list
you that they're
going to want to come back um you know I think yeah part of engaging them is
thinking about what
makes you unique and if there's a hobby that you've got or something that you
really love it's going
to show when you talk about it you're going to light up and it's going to show
so just bringing
something that you love to it or something that you enjoy or something you like
wearing even or
games you like playing or whatever just talking about whatever it is that makes
you unique I think
it's a really good idea um and also I know it's not the same for everyone but
for me
I just don't talk on camp very often I prefer to type because I just think it
takes so much
longer to type out a long fantasy than it does to talk it out and it's so much
less energy for me
so I personally prefer to type um and some people that have said that too have
been like
oh my god I didn't know I didn't have to talk on camp and I'm like oh my god
you're like everybody should know that it's totally up to you whether you want
to talk on camp or not
um yeah I feel you're out I'm exactly the same I've done this for 10 years now
and honestly I
have spoke like a handful of times I very rarely speak on camp and if I do like
I said it's just
10 on the mic on and just saying the odd word like hello and then that's it I'm
like back to
type and like I really don't like to talk on there for quite a few reasons and
yeah the main one is
same as yours it just takes so much longer to type it out and also when you're
typing it out you've
got more of a moment to actually think about what you want to type rather than
if you're just
talking it obviously that you can't wait for like 30 seconds in silence and
then responds
whereas when you're typing you know you don't even ask that you can be typing
you can be thinking
in like pretending to type while thinking about what you're typing you know
what I mean
so um yeah I don't feel the pressure to have to talk even if the clients want
you to it might
mean that they leave which is fine and that's happened to me many times over
the years they've
left because I haven't spoke but then another client will be right in your room
within however
long and then stay with you for a long time while you're typing and for me that
feels much better
better to me than to talk and you know keep those clients here that want me to
talk because
they'll be over and the conversation will be over faster anyway because I talk
too fast as it is so
um yeah I don't want a quick conversation um but I've wrote some tips down as
well I'll go through
if you're finished with yours L right yeah um one tip that I put on is to have
a competitive
rate for your price per minute so obviously I wish we could all charge you know
the top dollar
so much more than all the other girls on there but realistically if we have
really really high
price per minutes compared to everybody else on the website then why would the
client keep
coming back to us if we're charging so much more than everybody else although
we do deserve it
we definitely still need to be competitive with our rates so um I would just
always look
at the other girls online like say I've not been on for a couple of weeks or
whatever else or you
know even every every couple of months I like to do this just scroll through
the main page of
all over girls online and just take a look at roughly what the price per minute
is for
group chat and private chat so I would like to see the range so maybe I'll see
oh some girls have
their group chat at one credit a minute whereas others have a free but then
most people have it
around two let's say so nothing to myself okay so I'll position myself maybe
just a little bit above
what most people have like maybe um like 2.2 or 2.3 credits maybe I would do if
the range is
between one and three that's how I would do it myself and so you want to be
competitive but you
still want to you know still charge like what you're a little bit more than the
average I would say
that's how I would do it and so yeah definitely competitive rate for your price
per minute I think
is important um also your profile picture I mean we these are things that we
mention a lot but I
think it just these little you know little things are so important your profile
picture is what your
clients gonna see before they come with you and it's on the screen with
everybody else's in a very
small little box so you want it to be as eye-catching as possible um actually
one of my friends on
cam she puts a border around here photo so she'll have a normal profile photo
and then she'll
edit in like a border like exactly around the edge of like a bright colour so I
think she had like a
pink one in the past and it she really does stand out compared to everybody
else because I never
seen anybody else do that so I thought that was a great idea for her to do that
um and even with
the photo like with I've started to see recently like and change my mind on
things about like
how I'm presenting myself on there I feel about being as unique as possible is
what's really going
to draw people in so even if your photos a little bit like if you looked at it
properly it might
look a little bit weird like I don't know maybe the expression you're pulling
or the angle or this
or that but it will it'll be eye-catching because it's a bit different if you
know what I mean so I
think maybe trying to think outside of the box of your profile photo and not
just doing the
the normal you know generic one something that's going to draw people in
another one of my tips is to bid per hour another thing I say all the time but
every hour I go
online I bid for the front page unless I have a regular client who I'm meeting
on cam who I trust
100 percent that he's going to actually turn up then I will bother to bid I'll
just log on at any
time and he'll be there whereas if I'm just going on as normal um I always bid
every single hour put
you on the front page of the website way more people can view you um and I just
noticed that
I'm so much busier when I bid and when I'm not now I'm still okay when I don't
bid because I must
be in a lot of hot lists um which is something your client if you don't know
what a hot list is
your clients can add you into their hot list um so you're like saved in their
favourite folder let's
say basically it's what it is so every time you go online they get notified so
whether you're on
the front page or not they can see you're online so this is great but in the
beginning you're
probably not going to be on any hot list it takes time to build that up which
is fine so in that
time you can bid to be on the front page um another tip is to be consistent
especially if you want to
build up regulars the more consistent you are the better you want to do it's
that simple
um another tip is to do admin work around cam so on cam it's not just put on
the time in actually
being on cam it's the stuff outside of when you're on cam as well so applying
to emails
sending flirts updating your profile making content for your profile um content
that you can
sell content that's just going to be on your free gallery whatever it is um
doing the stuff
outside of actually being on cam is also very important to your success um two
more tips
um one of them is to come to our photo shoots so I think this is a great thing
for your cam career
as you will get more confidence at our shoots you'll get really amazing photos
and um yeah
I think it's just a very nice day for everyone and I think that it just
it does help with your common because you're just a little bit more connected
and involved and
like I said your photos that you got you can use them on your profile you can
maybe even sell them
um so yeah and finally my final tip is to live in a state of gratitude you are
literally your
own boss with this job you don't need to wake up to an alarm unless you want to
in my case
definitely not I hate getting up early to an alarm so I love this job and you
don't have to drag
yourself to work to a job that you don't like you do it from the comfort of
your beautiful home
you can work as little or as much as you like you know it's not that you have
do you have to go
to work now for eight hours a day or you know whatever it is you don't have to
you do as much
as you want or as little as you want everything is completely on your own terms
yeah of course
the clients are going to ask things of you but you do exactly what you want you
don't have to do
anything that you don't want to do and you can show up as whoever you like so
as you mentioned
previously on some days you can turn up as a dom some days you can turn up as a
bit more
like laid back you know whatever you want to turn up as you can and you just do
whatever
you're feeling on that day as well and yeah you can make so much money with
this so I just think
it's one of my like ultimate tips is to just be grateful for this job and trust
me your mindset
your state of like your how you are how you're feeling that is going to impact
your whole day
and impact how well you do on cam and also impact on the days when you're not
doing as well because
then you're still feeling like you know what even though I haven't made much
today I'm still grateful
because it's still a great job in tomorrow I'll probably do so good that you
know so yeah just
always live in a state of gratitude and yeah I feel like that will flow through
you and flow
through your conversations and you'll be a magnet to your clients because you
'll be just this ray of
beautiful energy that your clients will not want to turn away from so yeah
there are my tips
thank you very comprehensive tips yeah and I was thinking about that with your
last one as well
like I think it's a good thing to end on maybe good thing to remember that like
your clients
even if they're there for a few seconds or whatever every single client is
coming to see you
like they're coming for you they're coming because they've been attracted to
you because they want
to talk to you like they're coming for you so just remembering that because
yeah some people can
suffer with confidence and things but actually the fact that people will pay by
the minute just
to be in your presence not even your real life presence in your online presence
you know that's
amazing isn't it um so just feeling confident in the fact that yeah people will
pay literally just
to look at you um so if you can engage them then even better
um yeah so does anybody have any questions um
oh Sammy was just saying she always types it's much more enjoyable but yeah I
agree
um does anyone have any questions feel free to put something in the chat or any
tips that you want to
offer um anything at all while we're here
now well the groups are always open our WhatsApp's are open the group chats are
open so
you know feel free to leave a comment in there there's something that you haven
't that you can't
think of right now if you've got a question or just some feedback on the call
today that would be
amazing um thank you Sammy and yeah I hope everyone has a beautiful evening if
you're going on
cam I hope you feel inspired and you're gonna have a really great session on
cam and we'll see you
all very soon thank you thank you the woman everyone and see you good to see
you ladies
bye